Jack Ciroli



jvciroli@wpi.edu



linkedin.com/in/jack-ciroli



4016026018



https://jack353.github.io/resumeSite/

Summary

Experienced Software Developer with a demonstrated history of working with large and small teams. Skilled in JavaScript, Java, C/C++, and Python development. Recently graduated with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science from Worcester Polytechnic Institute.

Experience



+ Full-stack Developer Intern

New Breed

May 2022 - Aug 2022 (4 months)

Full Stack Development.

Part of an agile production team writing Node, SQL, HTML, and CSS implementing AWS frameworks and a diverse set of APIs.

Co-lead production of the Uponent Application.



Research Fellow

Worcester Polytechnic Institute

May 2021 - Aug 2021 (4 months)

Worked as a research fellow in the King Lab under Dr. Jean King and Dr. Benjamin Nephew.

Programmed fNIRS experiments using Python and PyschoPy, ran human subjects through trials, managed data collection, and managed and analyzed data.

Study was published in Elsevier Journal.

Education



Worcester Polytechnic Institute

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science

Aug 2019 - May 2023

Activities and societies: Tau Kappa Epsilon, Varsity Track & Field, Association of Computer Machinery

Skills

Agile Methodologies • Data Analysis • Python (Programming Language) • Java • Team Leadership • SQL • MATLAB • Data Collection • React.js • Node.js